

const questionsList =[{

    question: "In 'POTC1', Captain Jack Sparrow is first seen entering Port Royal on a small sinking boat. Who did he steal this boat from?",
    correctAnswer:"Anna-Maria",
    wrongAnswer1: "Lord Cutler Beckett",
    wrongAnswer2: "Will Turner",
    wrongAnswer3: "Governor Swann"},
  
    {question: "Whose line is this 'Ello Popet'?",
    correctAnswer:"Pintel",
    wrongAnswer1: "Bo'sun",
    wrongAnswer2: "Captain Barbossa",
    wrongAnswer3: "Captain Jack Sparrow"},
   
    {question: "What are the movies based on?",
    correctAnswer:"A ride at Disneyland",
    wrongAnswer1: "A video game",
    wrongAnswer2: "An old sea tale",
    wrongAnswer3: "A book"},
  
    {question: "What port did Captain Jack Sparrow sack without firing a single shot?",
    correctAnswer:"Nassau Port",
    wrongAnswer1: "Port Royal",
    wrongAnswer2: "Tortuga",
    wrongAnswer3: "Port Mason"},
  
    {question: "In POTC1, When Elizabeth was walking the plank, who said 'too long!' and stomped on the edge of the plank so she fell off?",
    correctAnswer:"Captain Barbossa",
    wrongAnswer1: "Captain Jack",
    wrongAnswer2: "Ragetti",
    wrongAnswer3: "Bo'sun"},
  
    {question: "Who says 'Aye! The compass doesn't point north! But we're not trying to find north are we?'",
    correctAnswer:"Joshamee Gibbs",
    wrongAnswer1: "Will Turner",
    wrongAnswer2: "Captain Jack Sparrow",
    wrongAnswer3: "Commodore Norrington"},
  
    {question: "How many Pirates of The Caribbean movies are there?",
    correctAnswer:"Not enough",
    wrongAnswer1: "Three",
    wrongAnswer2: "6",
    wrongAnswer3: "One"},
  
    {question: "What does Jack fall into after he retrieves the key?",
    correctAnswer:"An empty grave",
    wrongAnswer1: "A well",
    wrongAnswer2: "A pit of animal manure",
    wrongAnswer3: "The ocean"},
   
    {question: "Who's line was 'Bring me that horizon.'",
    correctAnswer:"Jack Sparrow",
    wrongAnswer1: "Will Turner",
    wrongAnswer2: "Gibbs",
    wrongAnswer3: "Pintel"},
  
    {question: "What nationality are the sailors that find Captain Jack's hat in POTC2?",
    correctAnswer:"Italian",
    wrongAnswer1: "Hungarian",
    wrongAnswer2: "Chinese",
    wrongAnswer3: "Greek"},

    {question: "What is captain Jack Sparrow's favorite drink?",
    correctAnswer:"Rum",
    wrongAnswer1: "Beer",
    wrongAnswer2: "Brandy",
    wrongAnswer3: "Wine"},

    {question: "What is POTC4 narrowly based on?",
    correctAnswer:"A Novel",
    wrongAnswer1: "A video game",
    wrongAnswer2: "A toy",
    wrongAnswer3: "A play"},

    {question: "What type of animal is the pet that Jack Sparrow hates?",
    correctAnswer:"Monkey",
    wrongAnswer1: "Bird",
    wrongAnswer2: "Snake",
    wrongAnswer3: "Dolphin"},

    {question: "What did Jack need from a mermaid at the Fountain of Youth?",
    correctAnswer:"A Tear",
    wrongAnswer1: "A tooth",
    wrongAnswer2: "A Kiss",
    wrongAnswer3: "A Hug"},

    {question: "What is Jack's favorite ship called?",
    correctAnswer:"The Black Pearl",
    wrongAnswer1: "The Flying Dutchman",
    wrongAnswer2: "The Drunken Pirate",
    wrongAnswer3: "The Matador"}
    
    ];